Guide to the Edward H. Boos Photographs 1897-1907
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana-Missoula
Edward H. Boos photographs
1897-1907
University of Montana, Mansfield Library, Archives and Special Collections The University of Montana—Missoula Missoula, MT 59812 406-243-2053 http://www.lib.umt.edu/asc library.archives@umontana.edu
Mss 672
Boos, Edward H., 1877-1937
2.5 linear feet
This collection includes photographs by Edward H. Boos,a photographer in Missoula, Montana, from 1897 through 1907. Broadly, the photographic subjects include the Missoula, Mission, and Flathead valleys in Montana; Kootenai, Salish and Pend'Oreille families on Montana's Flathead Reservation; and Glacier National Park and Yellowstone National Park. All images were taken near the beginning of the 20th Century.
Images 672.001 through 672.099 are glass plate negatives and thus probable originals. Images 672.291 through 672.309 are original film negatives. All other images are photograph prints. Where noted with the letters "DPL" preceding the image number, the originals are at the Denver Public Library. Duplicate numbers that are not preceded by DPL are held in collection Mss 346 (Edward Boos Photographs) at the Mansfield Library's Archives & Special Collections.
Biographical Note
Edward Boos was born in Kentucky on April 1, 1877. His family moved to Helena, Montana, while he was in grade school. He attended the University of Montana in Missoula, Montana in 1896 but did not complete a degree. In that same year Boos began working as a freelance correspondent for several newspapers in the Missoula area. During the summer of 1897 Boos accompanied the U.S. Army 25th Infantry Bicycle Corps on its experimental overland trip from Fort Missoula to St. Louis, Missouri. The company traversed 1,900 miles over difficult terrain and through taxing weather conditions in an attempt to prove that bicycles could replace horses for troop transport and reconnaissance. Boos submitted accounts of the expedition as they traveled. His accounts were prepared for the Daily Missoulian, but some were also published by newspapers along the route and a few were subsequently reprinted by national and international newspapers.
After the Bicycle Corps expedition Boos continued to produce photographs for western Montana newspapers. Sometime around 1900 he purchased his own camera and began photographing people and landscapes in the Missoula and Flathead valleys. Boos was particularly interested in recording life among the Kootenai, Salish and Pend'Oreille families of the Flathead Reservation as the 20th century began. He conducted a series of photographic portrait sessions at various sites across the reservation, mostly completed between spring and fall of 1905. According to a 1935 newspaper story, many of these portraits were developed at night under a canvas cover so the photographer could share the portraits directly with his subjects. Throughout the time period Boos continued to photograph landscapes and events in the Missoula and Flathead Lake areas.
In 1906 Boos accepted an advertising manager position with the Missoula Mercantile Company (MMS) and married Annie Hammond, cousin of MMC co-owner Andrew Hammond. Edward Boos ended his newspaper work but continued to periodically take photographs. Boos remained with the MMC for the next thirty-one years. In September 1935 an "Indian Jubilee" celebration was held in St. Ignatius, Montana. This event was the first public exhibition and print sale of Boos' Flathead Reservation portraits. Edward H. Boos died of a heart attack on September 26, 1937.
This collection mainly consists of glass plate negatives, film negatives and prints by Edward H. Boos,a photographer in Missoula, Montana, from 1897 through1907. Broadly, the photographic subjects include the Missoula, Mission, and Flathead valleys in Montana; Kootenai, Salish and Pend'Oreille families on Montana's Flathead Reservation; and Glacier National Park and Yellowstone National Park, all at the beginning of the 20th Century.
Some more specific photograph subjects include the Boos home, the Daly Horse Ranch (Riverside Farm / Bitterroot Stock Farm) near Hamilton, Montana, logging near Hamilton, the 25th Infantry Bicycle Corps, the Missoula Mercantile, and a Fourth of July parade in Missoula, Montana.
Also included are Boos' order booklets for "Flathead Indian Pictures."
The majority of the images in this collection have been individually described.
Researchers must use collection in accordance with the policies of Archives and Special Collections, the Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, and The University of Montana-Missoula.
These photographs remained in the possession of the Missoula Mercantile following Mr. Boos' death. Walter McLeod, a Mercantile owner, passed this group of glass plate negatives, film negatives, and photographs to his daughter who later passed them to her own daughter, Mary M. Pitch. For further explanation of overall Boos photograph custodial history, see Mss 346.
This collection of photographs was donated by Mary M. Pitch in November, 2006.
The Denver Public Library Western History/Genealogy Department retains a collection of 129 glass plate negatives and four additional prints by Edward Boos. Scanned images of all prints are available on-line from the Denver Public Library web site (http://digital.denverlibrary.org/). The Montana Historical Society and the Smithsonian Institution retain some prints from negatives at the Denver Public Library Western History/Genealogy Department and Mansfield Library Archives & Special Collections.
Mansfield Library's Archives & Special Collections also holds Mss 346, another collection of Boos photographs (some of which are duplicated in this collection), and two photos titled "Indian Dancing Men" and "Pielle-A Kootenai" in mats that are signed by Boos and include small pencil drawings.
This collection is indexed under the following headings in the online catalog. Researchers desiring materials about related topics, persons, or places should search the catalog using these headings.
United States. Army. Infantry Regiment, 25th. Bicycle Corps--Photographs.; Missoula Mercantile Company--Photographs.
Daly Horse Ranch (Mont.)--Photographs.; Flathead Indian Reservation (Mont.)--Photographs.; Flathead River Valley (B.C. and Mont.)--Photographs.; Glacier National Park (Mont.)--Photographs.; Mission Valley (Lake County, Mont.)--Photographs.; Missoula (Mont.)--Photographs.; Missoula (Mont.)--Buildings, structures, etc.--Photographs.; Missoula (Mont.)--Social life and customs--Photographs.; Missoula Valley (Mont.)--Photographs.; Yellowstone National Park--Photographs.
Dwellings--Montana--Missoula--Photographs; Families--Montana--Flathead Indian Reservations--Photographs; General stores--Montana--Missoula--Photographs; Indian reservations--Montana--Photographs; Indians of North America--Montana--Photographs; aLandscape photography--Montana; Logging--Montana--Photographs; Kalispel Indians--Photographs; Kootenai Indians--Photographs; Ranches--Montana--Photographs; Salish Indians--Photographs
Photographs
Montana; Native Americans; Agriculture; City and Town Life
- Boos' Home: Woman in front yard and garden, undated (Box 1, Photo number 672-001)
- Boos' Home: Front and side of house; Sidewalk on front and side, undated (Box 1, Photo number 672-002)
- Boos' Home: Women next to circular garden at side of house, undated (Box 1, Photo number 672-003)
- Boos' Home: Circular garden, undated (Box 1, Photo number 672-004)
- Boos' Home: Circular garden at side of house, undated (Box 1, Photo number 672-005)
- Boos' Home: Front and side of house, undated (Box 1, Photo number 672-006)
- Boos' Home: Front of house without ivy, undated (Box 1, Photo number 672-007)
- Boos' Home: Woman sitting on front porch step, undated (Box 1, Photo number 672-008)
- Boos' Home: Front and right side of house, undated (Box 1, Photo number 672-009)
- Boos' Home: Room with Indian photos and artifacts, undated (Box 1, Photo number 672-010)
- Boos' Home: 6 photos of Indians on display board, undated (Box 1, Photo number 672-011)
- Boos' Home: 6 photos of Indians on display board, undated (Box 1, Photo number 672-012)
- Boos' Home: 4 photos of Indians on display board, undated (Box 1, Photo number 672-013)
- Room 13, undated (Box 1, Photo number 672-014)
- Room 13: "Indian Corner", undated (Box 1, Photo number 672-015)
- Room 13: "Indian Corner", undated (Box 1, Photo number 672-016)
- Room 13, undated (Box 1, Photo number 672-017)
- Native American campground, undated (Box 1, Photo number 672-018)
- Teepees in a row, unknown location, undated (Box 1, Photo number 672-019)
- Chief Kae Kae She standing in front of teepee, undated (Box 1, Photo number 672-020)
  Duplicate of 78-264
- E-lum-ski-em (Antoine and Family), undated (Box 1, Photo number 672-021)
  Duplicate of 78-169
- Wat Yat-Mas -White Brant, undated (Box 1, Photo number 672-022)
  Duplicate of 78-208
- Charles Mot La Mon, undated (Box 1, Photo number 672-023)
  Duplicate of DPL# BS-68
- Kai-Kai (She's Grandchild), standing with dog, undated (Box 1, Photo number 672-024)
- Secretary [James R.] Garfield, Chief Larrison, and sons, circa 1907 (Box 1, Photo number 672-025)
  Duplicate of 78-192
- Flathead Indian Council, undated (Box 1, Photo number 672-026)
  Duplicate of DPL# BS-8
- Frank Carmille's Family, undated (Box 1, Photo number 672-027)
  Duplicate of 78-212
- Kai-Kai (She's Grandchild), undated (Box 1, Photo number 672-028)
- Sum-Knay (Grizzly Bear), undated (Box 1, Photo number 672-029)
- Buffalo Herd, undated (Box 2, Photo number 672-030)
- Buffalo Herd, man on horse in background, undated (Box 2, Photo number 672-031)
- Buffalo Near Trees (No. 1 photo by Nat Little), undated (Box 2, Photo number 672-032)
- Buffalo; man on horse in background, undated (Box 2, Photo number 672-033)
- Buffalo; man on horse in background, undated (Box 2, Photo number 672-034)
- "Relics of the Past"; Buffalo in the shadow of the Missions, 1899 (Box 2, Photo number 672-035)
  Duplicate of 72-20
- Buffalo shedding, 1899 (Box 2, Photo number 672-036)
- Buffalo at Rest, undated (Box 2, Photo number 672-037)
- Buffalo: People in pond fully clothed, undated (Box 2, Photo number 672-038)
- Buffalo: Some grazing., undated (Box 2, Photo number 672-039)
- Mission Range Panorama, undated (Box 2, Photo number 672-040)
- Mission Range Panorama, undated (Box 2, Photo number 672-041)
- Mission Range Panorama, undated (Box 2, Photo number 672-042)
- View of bridge from river bank, undated (Box 2, Photo number 672-043)
- Bridal Veil Falls, undated (Box 2, Photo number 672-044)
- Bridal Veil Falls, undated (Box 2, Photo number 672-045)
- Unidentified man fishing, undated (Box 2, Photo number 672-046)
- Unidentified men holding up strings of fish, undated (Box 2, Photo number 672-047)
- "A Roadside Repair"; An unidentified man changing bike tire, undated (Box 2, Photo number 672-048)
- The University, 1904 (Box 2, Photo number 672-049)
- The University-Path to University Hall, 1904 (Box 2, Photo number 672-050)
- University Hall, 1904 (Box 2, Photo number 672-051)
- Missoula Mercantile Company Exterior display windows, undated (Box 2, Photo number 672-052)
- Missoula Mercantile Company Exterior display windows, undated (Box 2, Photo number 672-053)
- Missoula Mercantile Company Exterior corner of building, undated (Box 2, Photo number 672-054)
- Missoula Mercantile Company Exterior corner display, undated (Box 2, Photo number 672-055)
- Missoula Mercantile Company Exterior corner of building, undated (Box 2, Photo number 672-056)
- Missoula Mercantile Company Exterior corner, display side, undated (Box 2, Photo number 672-057)
- Missoula Mercantile Company Canned goods display, undated (Box 2, Photo number 672-058)
- Fourth of July Parade, D.J. Donahue Company Float, undated (Box 2, Photo number 672-059)
- Fourth of July Parade, Missoula Mercantile Float, undated (Box 2, Photo number 672-060)
- Fourth of July Parade, Medieval Theme Float, undated (Box 2, Photo number 672-061)
- Fourth of July Parade, Medieval Float, undated (Box 2, Photo number 672-062)
- Fourth of July Parade, Statue of Liberty Float, undated (Box 2, Photo number 672-063)
- Fourth of July Parade, Elk's float, undated (Box 2, Photo number 672-064)
- Fourth of July Parade, Float carrying girls with state banners, undated (Box 2, Photo number 672-065)
- Fourth of July Parade, Log cabin float, undated (Box 2, Photo number 672-066)
- Daly Ranch Horse and undentified man, undated (Box 3, Photo number 672-067)
- Daly Ranch horse and unidentified man, undated (Box 3, Photo number 672-068)
- Daly Ranch Horses, boy on horse-drawn sulky, undated (Box 3, Photo number 672-069)
- Daly Ranch Horses, horse-drawn sulky with boy, undated (Box 3, Photo number 672-070)
- Daly Ranch Horses, boy in horse-drawn sulky, undated (Box 3, Photo number 672-071)
- Daly Ranch Horses, boy in horse-drawn sulky, undated (Box 3, Photo number 672-072)
- Daly Ranch Horses, 1st Premium Ribbon, undated (Box 3, Photo number 672-073)
- Daly Ranch Horses, boy on horse, undated (Box 3, Photo number 672-074)
- Daly Ranch Horses, boy on horse, undated (Box 3, Photo number 672-075)
- Daly Ranch Horses, boy on horse, undated (Box 3, Photo number 672-076)
- Daly Ranch Horse and unidentified man and children, undated (Box 3, Photo number 672-077)
- Daly Ranch Horse, 1st Premium Ribbon, undated (Box 3, Photo number 672-078)
- Daly Ranch Horse, undated (Box 3, Photo number 672-079)
- Daly Ranch Horse and unidentified man, undated (Box 3, Photo number 672-080)
- Daly Ranch Horses, unidentified men riding horses around track, undated (Box 3, Photo number 672-081)
- Daly Ranch Horse, undated (Box 3, Photo number 672-082)
- Daly Ranch Horse and buggy. Man (Edward H. Boos?) in buggy, undated (Box 3, Photo number 672-083)
- Daly Ranch Horse, Man in horse-drawn buggy (Edward H. Boos?), undated (Box 3, Photo number 672-084)
- Daly Ranch Horses, Man on horse-drawn sulky, undated (Box 3, Photo number 672-085)
- Daly Ranch Horses, Man on horse-drawn buggy, undated (Box 3, Photo number 672-086)
- Daly Ranch Horses, Horse and wagon with man and women Missoula, MT, undated (Box 3, Photo number 672-087)
- Daly Ranch Horse, Horseand wagon with man and woman in Missoula, MT, undated (Box 3, Photo number 672-088)
- Daly Ranch Horses with wagon and 2 men, undated (Box 3, Photo number 672-089)
- Daly Ranch Horses, Man in horse-drawn sulky, undated (Box 3, Photo number 672-090)
- Logging over Hamilton, Logging cars and Caboose, 1900 (Box 3, Photo number 672-091)
- Logging over Hamilton, Men on logs, 1900 (Box 3, Photo number 672-092)
- Logging over Hamilton, Loaded logging train, 1900 (Box 3, Photo number 672-093)
- Logging over Hamilton, Men loading logs on Northern Pacific Car, 1900 (Box 3, Photo number 672-094)
- Logging over Hamilton, Northern Pacific Railway Engine 104, 1900 (Box 3, Photo number 672-095)
- Logging over Hamilton, Northern Pacific Railway Engine 104, 1900 (Box 3, Photo number 672-096)
- Logging over Hamilton, Man on loaded logging wagon, 1900 (Box 3, Photo number 672-097)
- Logging over Hamilton, Men loading logs on Northern Pacific Car, 1900 (Box 3, Photo number 672-098)
- Logging over Hamilton, Loaded logging cars; Log piles and Clean cut in background, 1900 (Box 3, Photo number 672-099)
- Buffalo "in the shadow of the Missions", 1899 (Box 4, Photo number 672-100)
- Days work done, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-101)
  Duplicate of 78-391
- Isabelle with papoose and child, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-102)
  Duplicate of 78-157
- Child in a cradleboard, Leaning on a tree, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-103)
  Duplicate of 78-159
- The Parade, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-104)
  Duplicate of 78-187
- The Parade, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-105)
- Sin-se-la, White Brant, Alex-on, Sam Moody (Nat-yat-Mas-Hi-Hi, White Bird), 1905 (Box 4, Photo number 672-106)
  Duplicate of 78-194
- Preparing for Squaw Parade (Saddling horses, large camp), undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-107)
  Duplicate of 78-209
- Flathead Indian Council, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-108)
  Duplicate of 78-211 and DPL# BS-8
- Joseph Standing Bear and Lucy, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-109)
  Duplicate of 78-217
- See La, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-110)
  Duplicate of 78-222
- Alex Kinser in Dance Outfit (Arlee, MT), undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-111)
  Duplicate of 78-246
- Paul Lumphrey, Louis Lefthand, Chim-e-en Paul, Peter Stinins, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-112)
  Duplicate of 78-247
- Lodge Under Construction, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-113)
  Duplicate of 78-255 and DPL# BS-109
- Vi-tal, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-114)
  Duplicate of 78-253 and DPL# BS-91
- Flathead Lake During the High Water, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-115)
  Duplicate of 78-333
- Moonlight on Flathead Lake, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-116)
  Duplicate of 78-334
- Pend'Oreille Falls, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-117)
  Duplicate of 78-335
- Rocks at Lolo ot Springs #1, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-118)
  Duplicate of 78-338
- Foot of Flathead Lake, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-119)
  Duplicate of 78-339
- Bicycle Float; Entry into 4th of July Parade, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-120)
  Duplicate of 78-340
- Lake McDonald, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-121)
  Duplicate of 78-342
- Flathead Bay, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-122)
  Duplicate of 78-344
- Sunset, Pine Street, Missoula, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-123)
  Duplicate of 78-345
- South Missoula, July 4, 1904 (Box 4, Photo number 672-124)
  Duplicate of 78-348
- French Town Valley looking toward Missoula, June 5, 1904 (Box 4, Photo number 672-125)
  Duplicate of 78-361
- Bonner Bridge, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-126)
  Duplicate of 78-378
- Bonner Dam, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-127)
  Duplicate of 78-381
- Needle Point Rock Formation [Unknown Location], undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-128)
  Duplicate of 78-383
- Fishing on Lolo, 1907 (Box 4, Photo number 672-129)
  Duplicate of 78-386
- Rocks at Lolo Hot Springs, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-130)
  Duplicate of 78-387
- Garden City Brewery, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-131)
  Duplicate of 78-401
- Winter on the Rattlesnake, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-132)
  Duplicate of 78-418
- Hansen Creek, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-133)
  Duplicate of 78-423
- On Lake Blaine, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-134)
  Duplicate of 78-426
- Harvesting Grain; Horse drawn harvester, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-135)
  Duplicate of 78-431
- Mission Range from the Foot of Flathead, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-136)
  Duplicate of 78-433
- Old Sleugh; Flathead Reservation, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-137)
- Pigs, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-138)
  Duplicate of 78-438
- A Ranch Landscape; Unknown Location, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-139)
  Duplicate of 78-439
- The Race [Horse Race, Unknown Location], undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-140)
  Duplicate of 78-441
- Higgins Avenue, July 4, 1904 (Box 4, Photo number 672-141)
  Duplicate of 78-444
- Pend'Oreille Falls, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-142)
  Duplicate of 78-445
- View on Island [Unknown Location], undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-143)
  Duplicate of 78-446
- Missoula and Jumbo from South Side, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-144)
  Duplicate of 78-447
- Inquisitive Calves [Unknown Location], undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-145)
  Duplicate of 78-448
- Mission Creek, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-146)
  Duplicate of 78-450
- On the Road to Kalispell, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-147)
  Duplicate of 78-452
- Lake McDonald Reflection, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-148)
  Duplicate of 78-454
- Pend'Oreille Falls, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-149)
  Duplicate of 78-455
- Fredensburg Hill, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-150)
  Duplicate of 78-461
- Cascade Falls, Lightning Creek, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-151)
  Duplicate of 78-462
- Victoria B.C. Trip, Undated [Steamship] (Box 4, Photo number 672-152)
  Duplicate of 78-465
- 25th Infantry Bicycle Corps, circa 1897 (Box 4, Photo number 672-153)
  Duplicate of 73-31
- 25th Infantry Bicycle Corps standing in formation, circa 1897 (Box 4, Photo number 672-154)
  Duplicate of 80-47
- Boos' Home; 6 photos of Native American On Display Board, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-155)
- Boos' Home; 6 photos of Native American On Display Board, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-156)
- Boos' Home; 4 photos of Indians on Display Board, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-157)
- 3 Native American Portraits, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-158)
- Unidentified Native American Men standing near teepee, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-159)
- Mr. and Mrs. R.A. Eddy, Sin-se-La, Hi-hi, and Alexon, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-160)
- Boston Girl, Sin-se-la, Hi-hi, and Nora Toole, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-161)
- Native Americans riding through teepee village on horses, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-162)
- Native Americans riding on horses; one man carrying American flag, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-163)
- Native Americans receiving rations, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-164)
- Native Americans gathered around structure, some on horses and wagons, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-165)
- Kai-Kai (She's Grandchild), standing with dog, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-166)
- Native Americans on horseback, riding past row of tipis, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-167)
- "An Indian Ranch", undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-168)
- Reception of Secretary [James R.] Garfield; Major Belknap driving buggy, circa 1907 (Box 4, Photo number 672-169)
- Secretary Garfield in horse-drawn buggy driven by Major Belknap, circa 1907 (Box 4, Photo number 672-170)
- Reception of Secretary Garfield; Major Belknap driving buggy, circa 1907 (Box 4, Photo number 672-171)
- Unidentified Men on Horseback, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-172)
- Waterfall, Unidentified Location, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-173)
- Unidentified man in forest, Unknown Location, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-174)
- Road at base of Unidentified Mountain, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-175)
- Unidentified Lake and Mountains, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-176)
- Road, Unknown Location, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-177)
- Log Cabins and Unidentified men on horses, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-178)
- Unidentified Mountain and Creek, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-179)
- Unidentified Bridge, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-180)
- Road, Unknown Location, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-181)
- Unidentified Lake and Mountain, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-182)
- Glacier on Unidentified Mountain, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-183)
- Glacier Peak Looking North, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-184)
- Trail at Unknown Location, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-185)
- Unidentified River Bend, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-186)
- Unidentified River, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-187)
- Clouds Covering Unidentified Mountains, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-188)
- Unidentified Lake and Mountain, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-189)
- Landscape, Unknown Location, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-190)
- Landscape, Unknown Location, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-191)
- Unidentified Waterfall, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-192)
- Dead tree, Unknown Location, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-193)
- Unidentified Mountain and Lake, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-194)
- Unidentified Lake, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-195)
- Unidentified Mountain, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-196)
- Unidentified Mountain and Lake, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-197)
- Unidentified Mountain and Lake, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-198)
- Unidentified Mountains, undated (Box 4, Photo number 672-199)